

Mihai - Alexandru Ciubotariu

Date of birth: 15/06/1994 | **Nationality:** Romanian | **Gender:** Male

Phone number: (+40) 754272287 (Mobile) | Email address:

mihaiciubotariuro@gmail.com

Address: Şoseaua Copoului, nr. 89, 707406, Iaşi, Romania (Home)

ABOUT ME

I specialize in data processing and QA process. Paying close attention to details is fundamental to finding success at work. I love to continually learn what's new all things about web services.

I have a strong passion for the creativity and discipline that goes into my current job. In my free time, I enjoy being outdoors, listening to music, traveling and experiencing new and exciting adventures.

WORK EXPERIENCE

10/2021 - CURRENT Iasi, Romania

QA ENGINEER XIVIC INC.

- Assisting in all test activities related to functional, regression, integration, system load & performance testing.
- Executing manual testing of changes to a range of web & desktop applications, APIs & other platform components.
- Develop and maintain test plans based on use cases, requirements, design content and required test coverage.
- Report bugs and errors using best practices
- Participating in SCRUM meetings to actively contribute to estimation, issue resolution and delivery management.
- Understanding applications, platform and data at a very detailed level to maximize contribution.
- Continuous improvement and setting a high bar for the quality of delivery.
- Using tools optimally to enable detailed issue tracking and reporting.
- Performing root cause analysis exercises in pre-production and production environments.
- Assisting in all test activities related to functional, regression, integration, system load & performance testing.
- Executing manual testing of changes to a range of web & desktop applications, APIs & other platform components.
- Develop and maintain test plans based on use cases, requirements, design content and required test coverage.
- Report bugs and errors using best practices
- Participating in SCRUM meetings to actively contribute to estimation, issue resolution and delivery management.
- Understanding applications, platform and data at a very detailed level to maximize contribution.
- Continuous improvement and setting a high bar for the quality of delivery.
- Using tools optimally to enable detailed issue tracking and reporting.
- Performing root cause analysis exercises in pre-production and production environments.

11/11/2019 - 10/2021 Iași, Romania

SENIOR COMPLIANCE ASSOCIATE AMAZON DEVELOPMENT CENTER

- Handling the day-to-day volumes of the assigned tasks and easuring the quality standards are met;
- Maintaining records of day-to-day work by updating trackers to reflect work done;
- Escalating to the manager in a timely manner all quality related problems, or problems that reflect any deviation from the SOP agreed with the internal customers;
- Administrating all allocated processes that imply correcting and updating product descriptions and images for the items sold on Amazon websites;

- Managing Hazmat products and vendor orders, as well as creating specific and reoccurring reports for internal customers;
- Offering support to vendors with regards to the process of setting up items on the Amazon websites;

Business or Sector Information and communication | Address Strada Sfântul Lazăr nr. 27, 700045, Iasi, Romania |

Website www.amazon.com

21/07/2021 - 09/2021 Iasi, Romania

MANUAL QA PENTALOG

- Review and analyze product / system specifications
- Create and execute test scenarios
- Perform functional and non-functional testing
- Design, maintain and update test cases based on the requirement specification;
- Participate in test case peer reviews with QA and other team members
- Report bugs and errors using best practices
- Help troubleshoot issues
- Help with the status report of testing activities
- Help on production release testing phase

Business or Sector Information and communication | Website https://stagiu.pentalog.ro/#/welcome

01/08/2018 - 31/08/2019 lasi

GLOBAL REPUBLISH TASK GFK ROMÂNIA

Subject Matter Expert (Global Position)

- Communicating with teams/colleagues from other global teams.
- Receiving and processing various request in a timely manner via JIRA and DWH.
- Ability to work with a large quantity of requests.
- Analytical mind and able to provide solutions to problems.
- Excellent attention to detail.
- Clear and professional written and verbal communication skills.
- Going the extra mile when deadlines occur and assuring that processes that follow will be handled as soon as possible.
- Able to effectively deliver tasks and projects against deadlines.
- · Able to work independently.

16/06/2014 - 31/07/2018 Iasi, Romania

DATA PROCESSING ASSISTANT GFK ROMÂNIA

Junior Coder - Coder - Senior Coder - Specialist Coder

- Improved the error rate of matching products up to 98% by paying close attention to details.
- Completed deadlines regardless of the circumstances daily, weekly and/or monthly.
- Strengthened team working spirit by having to work in a minimum of 3 colleagues per team in every project allocated.
- Single-handedly completed projects when necessary with all the side work and direct contact via e-mail.
- Organized and distributed work when needed.
- Support offering and cross-activity when needed.
- · Mentoring and training new colleagues.

2010 - 09/2014 laşi

FREELANCER

- Fixing problems with existing projects (mostly WordPress).
- Edited HTML/CSS/JavaScript and plugins via WordPress/WPengine
- (Re)writing WordPress plugins to customize WordPress experience.
- Create website layout/user interface by using standard HTML/CSS practices.
- Installing packages via cPanel

- Be responsibile for maintaining, expanding the websites created.
- Increased traffic and enhanced page ranking by improving website structure, performing Search Engine Optimization (SEO) and Search Engine Marketing (SEM) for local improvements.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2017 - 15/06/2020 Iași, Romania

COMMUNICATION AND PUBLIC RELATIONS - ID Faculty of Philosophy and Social-Political University

Website https://www.fssp.uaic.ro/ | Field of study Communication and Public Relations | Final grade 8,12 |

Level in EQF EQF level 5 | **Type of credits** ECTS | **Number of credits** 180 |

Thesis Optimizing a web page in a search engine

15/09/2009 - 15/06/2013 Iași, Romania

TELECOMMUNICATIONS TECHNICIAN Technical College of Transport lași

Level in EQF EQF level 3

15/09/2000 - 15/06/2009 Iași, Romania

GYMNASIUM National Pedagogical College "Vasile Lupu"

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ROMANIAN**

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
FRENCH	B1	B1	A2	A2	B1
ENGLISH	B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

JOB-RELATED SKILLS

Job-related skills

I'm pretty good at resolving problems, details, and web technology. Although those 3 skills are not unique, being able to combine them and apply them at work, makes me a "go-to" person. Whenever the organization is facing a problem, I will use an analytical approach to find a solution, organize it into easy-to-understand text for the client, and present the solution to resolve quick in a clear and effective manner. Also autonomy, discipline, perseverance in the learning process.